(this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-app"]||[]).push([[0],{12:function(t,e,o){t.exports=o(19)},17:function(t,e,o){},18:function(t,e,o){},19:function(t,e,o){"use strict";o.r(e);var n=o(0),s=o.n(n),r=o(6),a=o.n(r),c=(o(17),o(7)),i=o(8),u=o(2),l=o(11),h=o(10),m=function(){return s.a.createElement("h1",{className:"text-center mb-5"},"Quiz App")},d=function(t){var e=t.value;return s.a.createElement("h4",{className:"mb-4"},e)},p=function(t){var e=t.index,o=t.text,n=t.checkAnswer,r=t.correctAnswerIndex,a=t.showIndicator;return s.a.createElement("button",{className:"answerBtn form-control mb-2 ".concat(!0===a&&r===e?"correct":""),type:"button",onClick:function(){return n(e)}},o)},w=function(t){var e=t.options,o=t.checkAnswer,n=t.correctAnswerIndex,r=t.showIndicator;return s.a.createElement("div",{className:"form-group"},e.map((function(t,e){return s.a.createElement(p,{key:e,index:e,text:t,correctAnswerIndex:n,showIndicator:r,checkAnswer:o})})))},f=o(9),b=(o(18),o(21)),v=function(t){Object(l.a)(o,t);var e=Object(h.a)(o);function o(t){var n;return Object(c.a)(this,o),(n=e.call(this,t)).state={qaList:f,question:"",options:[],correctAnswer:"",showIndicator:!1,isCorrect:null,score:0,round:0,progress:0},n.checkAnswer=n.checkAnswer.bind(Object(u.a)(n)),n}return Object(i.a)(o,[{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){this.shuffleArray(this.state.qaList),this.getQuestion(),console.log(this.state.qaList)}},{key:"checkAnswer",value:function(t){var e=this;this.setState({round:this.state.round+1},(function(){e.setState({progress:Math.ceil(e.state.round/e.state.qaList.length*100)}),e.state.round<e.state.qaList.length?(t===e.state.correctAnswerIndex&&e.setState({score:e.state.score+1}),e.setState({isCorrect:t===e.state.correctAnswerIndex,showIndicator:!0}),e.nextQuestion()):e.state.round===e.state.qaList.length&&(console.log("GAME OVER"),alert("SCORE: ".concat(e.state.score,"/").concat(e.state.round)))}))}},{key:"nextQuestion",value:function(){var t=this;setTimeout((function(){t.getQuestion(),t.setState({isCorrect:null,showIndicator:!1}),document.activeElement.blur()}),1500)}},{key:"getQuestion",value:function(){this.setState({question:this.state.qaList[this.state.round].question,options:this.state.qaList[this.state.round].opt,correctAnswerIndex:this.state.qaList[this.state.round].correct})}},{key:"shuffleArray",value:function(t){for(var e=t.length-1;e>0;e--){var o=Math.floor(Math.random()*(e+1)),n=[t[o],t[e]];t[e]=n[0],t[o]=n[1]}return t}},{key:"render",value:function(){return s.a.createElement("div",{className:"main"},s.a.createElement(m,null),s.a.createElement(d,{value:this.state.question}),s.a.createElement(w,{options:this.state.options,correctAnswerIndex:this.state.correctAnswerIndex,checkAnswer:this.checkAnswer,showIndicator:this.state.showIndicator}),s.a.createElement(b.a,{now:this.state.progress,label:"".concat(this.state.progress,"%"),variant:100==this.state.progress?"success":""}))}}]),o}(s.a.Component);Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));a.a.render(s.a.createElement(s.a.StrictMode,null,s.a.createElement(v,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(t){t.unregister()})).catch((function(t){console.error(t.message)}))},9:function(t){t.exports=JSON.parse('[{"question":"What is the largest mammal?","opt":["Dog","Cat","Horse","All the same"],"correct":3},{"question":"How does one gain the ability to fly?","opt":["You fly","Become birb","Not possible","Just do it"],"correct":1},{"question":"If I can fly in my dreams, am I a birb?","opt":["Yes","No","Maybe","Perhaps"],"correct":0},{"question":"How many dogs exist?","opt":["5","10","666","5 594 338 000"],"correct":2},{"question":"What is 5+5?","opt":["5","No","10","Not a number"],"correct":2},{"question":"How many cats are needed?","opt":["75756","429347573275","5","None"],"correct":2},{"question":"What is love?","opt":["Baby don\'t hurt me","Don\'t hurt me","No more","An illusion ;_;"],"correct":3},{"question":"What is the radius of you\'re house? (in meters)","opt":["5","285","420","10000"],"correct":2},{"question":"What is the mass of the Sun? (in tonnes)","opt":["A lot","500","5","The Sun has no mass"],"correct":1},{"question":"How fast does light travel?","opt":["5","Yes","Fast","At the speed of light"],"correct":3},{"question":"What are birbs actually?","opt":["Surveillance drones","Horses","Birbs","Borbs"],"correct":0},{"question":"How is it possible to get a horse?","opt":["It\'s not possible","Horses are not real","Just get it","Bribe the government"],"correct":3}]')}},[[12,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.14b2e86a.chunk.js.map